<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<softwarelist>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Action Hero 3D: Wild Dog" URL="/zeebo/991386-action-hero-3d-wild-dog">
		<Description>Action Hero 3D: Wild Dog is an Action game, developed and published by Com2uS,  which was released in South America in 2009.</Description>
		<UserRating>3.00 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Just Right</Difficulty>
		<Length>1 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Com2uS</Developer>
		<Genre>Action &gt; General</Genre>
		<Release name="Action Hero 3D: Wild Dog" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Com2uS</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>05/29/09</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Alice no Pais das Maravilhas" URL="/zeebo/620246-alice-no-pais-das-maravilhas">
		<Description>Alice no Pais das Maravilhas is an Action game, developed and published by Disney Interactive Studios,  which was released in South America in 2010.</Description>
		<Developer>Disney Interactive Studios</Developer>
		<Genre>Action &gt; Platformer &gt; 2D</Genre>
		<Release name="Alice no Pais das Maravilhas" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Disney Interactive Studios</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>11/09/10</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Alien Breaker Deluxe" URL="/zeebo/611151-alien-breaker-deluxe">
		<Description>Alien Breaker Deluxe is a Puzzle game, developed and published by Vega Mobile,  which was released in South America in 2010.</Description>
		<Developer>Vega Mobile</Developer>
		<Genre>Puzzle &gt; General</Genre>
		<Release name="Alien Breaker Deluxe" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Vega Mobile</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>05/20/10</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Alpine Racer" URL="/zeebo/991385-alpine-racer">
		<Description>Alpine Racer is a Sports game, developed and published by Namco Bandai Games,  which was released in South America in 2009.</Description>
		<Developer>Namco Bandai Games</Developer>
		<Genre>Sports &gt; Individual &gt; Ski / Snowboard</Genre>
		<Release name="Alpine Racer" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Namco Bandai Games</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>05/29/09</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Armageddon Squadron" URL="/zeebo/611152-armageddon-squadron">
		<Description>Polarbit present Armageddon Squadron, an arcade flight simulator giving you control of some of the best known aircraft of the WWII era in a variety of mission types and environments.Objectives include bombing and strafing raids against facilities and convoys, protection of ground troops against enemy aircraft and action-packed dogfights against enemy aces. Prepare to unleash an arsenal of machine guns, bombs, rockets and torpedoes above lush, green countryside, open sea and battle-pocked cities.Features:Beautiful 3D graphicsSmooth accelerometer controlsExtensive campaign mode, time trial courses and arcade modeInternet multiplayer</Description>
		<Developer>Polarbit</Developer>
		<Genre>Simulation &gt; General</Genre>
		<Release name="Armageddon Squadron" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Polarbit</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>09/25/10</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Bad Dudes Vs. DragonNinja" URL="/zeebo/611153-bad-dudes-vs-dragonninja">
		<Description>The opponents in your battle for supremacy are four types of Evil Ninja star-throwing Assassins whose skills are many and dangerous! Also out to spoil your day are Acrobatic Women Warriors and vicious Guard Dogs. At the end of each level you must overcome the Ninja Master in order to progress. Some examples of these superhuman villains are: A fire-breathing Fat Man, an Armor Clad Giant and the Green and Gruesome Giant Ninja - who has a disconcerting habit of suddenly multiplying into an army!</Description>
		<UserRating>4.67 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Just Right</Difficulty>
		<Length>2.5 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Data East</Developer>
		<Genre>Action &gt; Beat-'Em-Up &gt; 2D</Genre>
		<Release name="Bad Dudes Vs. DragonNinja" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>G-mode</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>07/27/10</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Bejeweled Twist" URL="/zeebo/991443-bejeweled-twist">
		<Description>Spin, match, explode WOW! Its a brilliant new way to play Bejeweled, from PopCap. Spin and match explosive gems for shockwaves of fun. Rotate jewels to set up electrifying combos, outwit surprising obstacles like Locks and Bombs, and create high-voltage Flame and Lightning gems.
When you want to dial up the intensity, go for Challenge mode or five-minute Blitz. And if relaxing is more your style, kick up your feet with stress-free Zen. No matter the mode, youll discover new strategies, improve your moves, and find endless ways to win!</Description>
		<UserRating>5.00 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Easy</Difficulty>
		<Length>80+ hours</Length>
		<Developer>PopCap</Developer>
		<Franchise>Bejeweled</Franchise>
		<Genre>Puzzle &gt; Matching</Genre>
		<Release name="Bejeweled Twist" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>PopCap</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>09/29/09</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Boomerang Sports Peteca" URL="/zeebo/646763-boomerang-sports-peteca">
		<Description>Boomerang Sports Peteca is a Sports game, developed and published by Tec Toy,  which was released in South America in 2010.</Description>
		<Developer>Tec Toy</Developer>
		<Genre>Sports &gt; Individual &gt; Tennis</Genre>
		<Release name="Boomerang Sports Peteca" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Tec Toy</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>05/13/10</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Boomerang Sports Queimada" URL="/zeebo/991444-boomerang-sports-queimada">
		<Description>Boomerang Sports Queimada is a Sports game, developed and published by Tec Toy,  which was released in South America in 2010.</Description>
		<Developer>Tec Toy</Developer>
		<Genre>Sports &gt; Individual &gt; Other</Genre>
		<Release name="Boomerang Sports Queimada" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Tec Toy</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>02/05/10</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Boomerang Sports Tennis" URL="/zeebo/991445-boomerang-sports-tennis">
		<Description>Boomerang Sports Tennis is a Sports game, developed and published by Tec Toy,  which was released in South America in 2009.</Description>
		<Developer>Tec Toy</Developer>
		<Genre>Sports &gt; Individual &gt; Tennis</Genre>
		<Release name="Boomerang Sports Tennis" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Tec Toy</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>10/15/09</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Boomerang Sports Volei" URL="/zeebo/991446-boomerang-sports-volei">
		<Description>Boomerang Sports Volei is a Sports game, developed and published by Tec Toy,  which was released in South America in 2009.</Description>
		<Developer>Tec Toy</Developer>
		<Genre>Sports &gt; Team &gt; Volleyball</Genre>
		<Release name="Boomerang Sports Volei" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Tec Toy</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>12/14/09</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Brain Challenge" URL="/zeebo/991384-brain-challenge">
		<Description>Get your brain in shape with fun daily exercises-these challenging and entertaining puzzles act like a vitamin boost for your brain. Twenty different games in five categories (Memory, Visual, Logic, Math, and Focus) will train all areas of your brain. Brain Challenge is more than just a game, it's your personal coach for mental fitness!</Description>
		<UserRating>4.25 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Tough</Difficulty>
		<Length>12 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Gameloft</Developer>
		<Genre>Miscellaneous &gt; Edutainment</Genre>
		<Release name="Brain Challenge" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Gameloft</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>05/29/09</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Caveman Ninja" URL="/zeebo/996102-caveman-ninja">
		<Description>Caveman Ninja is an Action game, developed by Data East and published by G-mode,  which was released in South America in 2010.</Description>
		<UserRating>4.75 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Just Right</Difficulty>
		<Length>4 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Data East</Developer>
		<Franchise>Joe &amp; Mac</Franchise>
		<Genre>Action &gt; Platformer &gt; 2D</Genre>
		<Release name="Caveman Ninja" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>G-mode</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>04/16/10</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Crash Bandicoot Nitro Kart 3D" URL="/zeebo/991383-crash-bandicoot-nitro-kart-3d">
		<Description>The richest 3D kart racing experience! Speed your way through 12 thrilling tracks and multiple environments! Race and battle against zany opponents and turn them to dust with 8 devastating weapons. Tilt and twist your iPhone for truly "Nitro" driving sensations.Juego también disponible en español***** CHECK OUT MORE GAMES FROM ACTIVISION! *****Call of Duty: Zombies, Guitar Hero, Crash Bandicoot Nitro Kart 3D, Crash Bandicoot Nitro Kart 2, Tony Hawk’s Pro Skater 2, Cabela’s Dangerous Hunts, Rapala Pro Bass Fishing, Geometry Wars: Touch, and Pix Maze</Description>
		<UserRating>4.00 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Just Right</Difficulty>
		<Length>12 hours</Length>
		<Developer>VU Games</Developer>
		<Franchise>Crash Bandicoot</Franchise>
		<Genre>Racing &gt; Arcade &gt; Automobile</Genre>
		<Release name="Crash Bandicoot Nitro Kart 3D" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>VU Games</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>05/29/09</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Dark Seal" URL="/zeebo/996103-dark-seal">
		<Description>Dark Seal is an Action game, developed by Data East and published by G-mode,  which was released in South America in 2010.</Description>
		<Developer>Data East</Developer>
		<Genre>Action &gt; Beat-'Em-Up &gt; 2D</Genre>
		<Release name="Dark Seal" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>G-mode</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>05/04/10</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Disney's All-Star Cards" URL="/zeebo/611154-disneys-all-star-cards">
		<Description>Challenge your favorite Disney characters in a series of fun and fantastic card games in Disney’s All Star Cards.  The whole gang is here — Mickey, Minnie, Goofy, Donald, and Daisy — and each of their houses is themed with a different card game.

Choose from games like Go Fish, Hearts, Crazy 8’s, and a special surprise game!  Collect Pixie Dust to customize your cards and change the rules.  With dazzling animation, great music and surprises throughout, everyone’s a winner with Disney’s All Star Cards!

Disney makes other great games for you and your family. Look for Breakspin, Luma, Toy Story Mania, Disney Fairies Fly, Disney’s Magic Mirror, Disney Fireworks, and Disney Puzzle Family.  For more Disney fun, please visit Disney Online from your iPhone or iPod Touch browser.</Description>
		<Developer>Disney Mobile Studios</Developer>
		<Genre>Miscellaneous &gt; General</Genre>
		<Release name="Disney's All-Star Cards" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Disney Mobile Studios</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>09/21/10</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Double Dragon" URL="/zeebo/991382-double-dragon">
		<Description>Double Dragon is the story of Billy and Jimmy Lee, twin brothers who learned to fight on the cold, tough streets of the city. Their expert knowledge of the martial arts combined with their street smarts, has made them both formidable fighting machines. But now Billy is faced with his greatest challenge. Marian has been kidnapped by the Black Warriors, the savage street gang of the mysterious Shadow Boss! Using whatever weapons come to hand - knives, whips, bats, rocks, oil drums, even dynamite - Billy must pursue the gang through the slums, factories, and wooded outskirts of the city to reach the hideout for his final confrontation with the Shadow Boss... his brother Jimmy!</Description>
		<UserRating>3.13 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Just Right</Difficulty>
		<Length>6 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Zeebo Inc.</Developer>
		<Franchise>Double Dragon</Franchise>
		<Genre>Action &gt; Beat-'Em-Up &gt; 2D</Genre>
		<Release name="Double Dragon" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Zeebo Inc.</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>05/29/09</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="FIFA 09" URL="/zeebo/991381-fifa-09">
		<Description>Powered by the third generation of the EA SPORTS football engine, FIFA 09 features more than 250 core gameplay additions and enhancements that deliver the most responsive, intelligent and realistic action ever for the series. Enjoy turning defenders with more controlled dribbling and ball control, snapping off precision shots with improved first-time shooting mechanics and firing beautifully timed passes with greater accuracy, placing the ball exactly where you want it. With new player momentum physics the speed and weight of the player determines everything from the distance of a slide tackle and the power of a header to the severity of player collisions and the height of a player's jump. Plus, players now behave according to their physical attributes with larger, stronger players dominating collisions, battles for control of the ball, and position in challenges for two player headers. FIFA 09 features new Custom Team Tactics that gives you all the tools to become a first-team coach. For the first time, go inside the game engine to customize the positioning and support play of your teammates and decide exactly how your team will play in any situation. Now you are the player, coach and manager! You have the power to adjust and customize tactical settings so CPU players and your team perform just like the real-world team plays or how you think it should play. Save your tactics and then make strategic decisions to exploit your opponent's weaknesses, all on-the-fly.</Description>
		<UserRating>3.25 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Easy</Difficulty>
		<Length>1 hours</Length>
		<Developer>EA Sports</Developer>
		<Franchise>FIFA Soccer</Franchise>
		<Genre>Sports &gt; Team &gt; Soccer &gt; Sim</Genre>
		<Release name="FIFA 09" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>EA Sports</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>05/29/09</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Galaxy On Fire" URL="/zeebo/991447-galaxy-on-fire">
		<Description>[Galaxy on Fire™, the original App Store classic that kicked off the most popular sci-fi series on iOS, is now available in a revised F2P version with re-balanced in-game economy and new features! Find out how it all began and learn more about the back story of Keith T. Maxwell, Mkkt Bkkt and Co!]# # #   STORY AND GAMEPLAY   # # # Galaxy on Fire™ is an epic space shooter and trader with adventure and RPG elements. In a huge galaxy with hundreds of planets and space stations, you take on the role of Keith T. Maxwell, a hot-headed fighter pilot who becomes a key figure in the Terran Forces’ hard-fought war against an aggressive alien race known as Vossk. In the course of the game’s main storyline, you’ll be working your way up from gun-for-hire to squadron leader and stand your ground in all kinds of ambitious missions and assignments. During your adventurous flights you can collect loot from the enemy vessels you’ve taken down and sell it in order to equip your own craft with better weapons and power-ups. Besides the regular story missions, you will also be able to take on various freelance missions – sometimes dubious and sometimes lucrative – which will be given to you by shady alien characters. If you want to progress faster, you can either obtain credit packs via in-app purchase or make use of a broad selection of offerwalls and other benefits. Of course, you can play the game fully without spending a single buck!# # #   TRUST THE MEDIA   # # # Galaxy on Fire™ has received raving reviews in almost all of the leading magazines and websites. While Pocket Gamer said that it is “phenomenally good [and will] change the way you think about mobile phone games forever”, AppGamer proclaimed that GOF “is now an ambassador of the iPhone”. # # #   TRUST THE FANS   # # #Thousands of fans have written 5-star reviews for Galaxy on Fire™ and called it “one of the best space fighter games on iTunes” (Oridin, 5 points out of 5) and “a fun game that allows you to play for hours” (Top Surgeon, 5 points out of 5).# # #   SPECIAL FEATURES OF GALAXY ON FIRE   # # # • 3D sci-fi shooter with trading system • Vast universe with hundreds of planets and space stations • Captivating story with lots of dialog and animated cut scenes• 10 unique spaceships with different stats and capabilities• Dozens of weapons, shields, drives and power-ups• More than 20 hours of exciting game play • Arcade-style survival mode# # #   JOIN THE COMMUNITY   # # #Get in touch with thousands of other Galaxy on Fire™ fans through our official website, forums and social media profiles! Official Galaxy on Fire™ Homepage - http://www.galaxyonfire.com/ Official Fishlabs Homepage - http://www.fishlabs.net/Official Fishlabs Forums - http://forums.fishlabs.net/en Like GOF on Facebook - http://www.facebook.com/galaxyonfire Like us on Facebook - http://www.facebook.com/fishlabs Follow us on Twitter - http://www.twitter.com/fishlabs Check us out on YouTube - http://www.youtube.com/fishlabsgames# # #   PREPARE YOURSELF FOR THE NEXT ADVENTURE   # # # Don’t miss the critically acclaimed sequel Galaxy on Fire 2™ and the two add-ons Valkyrie™ and Supernova™.Download GOF2 HD (for iPhone 5, new iPad, etc) on the App Store - http://bit.ly/gof2hdDownload GOF2 SD (for older iOS devices) on the App Store – http://bit.ly/gof2sd-EN# # #   HARDWARE REQUIREMENTS   # # #Galaxy on Fire™ runs smoothly on the iPhone 3GS and all subsequent iOS devices. It requires iOS 4.0 or higher.</Description>
		<Developer>Fishlabs</Developer>
		<Genre>Simulation &gt; Space &gt; Combat</Genre>
		<Release name="Galaxy On Fire" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Fishlabs</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>10/08/09</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Heavy Barrel" URL="/zeebo/611155-heavy-barrel">
		<Description>Heavy Barrel is an Action game, developed by Data East and published by G-mode,  which was released in South America in 2010.</Description>
		<Developer>Data East</Developer>
		<Genre>Action &gt; General</Genre>
		<Release name="Heavy Barrel" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>G-mode</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>07/27/10</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Heavy Weapon" URL="/zeebo/991448-heavy-weapon">
		<Description>It's shoot-'em-up arcade action at its best! Use an incredible assortment of heavy artillery to blast away enemy tanks and planes, and fight your way to victory. What are you waiting for? Pull yourself up by your bootstraps and get into the action!</Description>
		<Developer>PopCap</Developer>
		<Genre>Action &gt; Shooter &gt; Shoot-'Em-Up &gt; Vertical</Genre>
		<Release name="Heavy Weapon" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>PopCap</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>12/16/09</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Iron Sight" URL="/zeebo/611156-iron-sight">
		<Description>Iron Sight is a brand new 3D multiplayer game for all artillery game fans!Building on the tried and true gameplay of titles such as iShoot or Worms, but in highly detailed, beautiful 3D environments AND with online MULTIPLAYER!---PRESS QUOTES:"Get this game NOW! Outstanding game highly recommended 5/5"- iphoneapps-review.com"Dazzling graphics; enjoyable gameplay"- slidetoplay.com"If you liked iShoot, I am sure you will love this cool game called Iron Sight."- IPhoneIndiaBlog.com---Move your battle mechs, use their equipment and attack with a large range of weapons: homing missiles, artillery, cluster missiles and much more. Fight with real opponents in one of the MULTIPLAYER modes, or take a hazardous journey to the heart of war during 2 CAMPAINGS and multiple INSTANT ACTION missions.Features:- Dual campaigns and single mission game modes- Internet and hot-seat multiplayer- Wide arsenal of weapons- Beautiful 3D environments, high quality visuals, animation and sounds- Adjustable difficulty levels- In-game tutorial and easy-to-master controls</Description>
		<Developer>Polarbit</Developer>
		<Genre>Adventure &gt; General</Genre>
		<Release name="Iron Sight" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Polarbit</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>09/28/10</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Karnov's Revenge" URL="/zeebo/996104-karnovs-revenge">
		<Description>The quest to defeat the mysterious Baron of Battlers, the mysterious K, is on. In order to get to this grotesque gladiator, however, you need to fight your way through 11 matches with the most skilled, most deadly of all combatants in the world of physical contact. Use your powers of pulverization, psychic energy blasts, and ridiculous strength to become the explosive fighting god in FIGHTERS HISTORY DYNAMITE!</Description>
		<UserRating>4.83 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Just Right</Difficulty>
		<Length>1 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Data East</Developer>
		<Genre>Action &gt; Fighting &gt; 2D</Genre>
		<Release name="Karnov's Revenge" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>G-mode</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>04/16/10</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Magical Drop III" URL="/zeebo/995757-magical-drop-iii">
		<Description>Magical Drop III is a Puzzle game, developed by Data East and published by G-mode,  which was released in South America in 2010.</Description>
		<UserRating>4.50 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Just Right</Difficulty>
		<Length>8 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Data East</Developer>
		<Franchise>Magical Drop</Franchise>
		<Genre>Puzzle &gt; Matching</Genre>
		<Release name="Magical Drop III" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>G-mode</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>04/22/10</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Need for Speed Carbon: Own the City" URL="/zeebo/991380-need-for-speed-carbon-own-the-city">
		<Description>What starts in the city is settled in the canyons as Need for Speed Carbon immerses you into the world's most dangerous and adrenaline-filled form of street racing. You and your crew must race in an all-out war for the city, risking everything to take over your rivals' neighborhoods one block at a time. As the police turn up the heat, the battle ultimately shifts to Carbon Canyon, where territories and reputations can be lost on every perilous curve. Need for Speed Carbon delivers the next generation of customization giving you the power to design and tweak your crew's cars in every way using the ground-breaking new Autosculpt technology. Represent your car class, your crew, and your turf in Need for Speed Carbon, the next revolution in racing games.</Description>
		<UserRating>3.92 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Just Right</Difficulty>
		<Length>29.5 hours</Length>
		<Developer>EA Games</Developer>
		<Franchise>Need for Speed</Franchise>
		<Genre>Racing &gt; Simulation &gt; Automobile</Genre>
		<Release name="Need for Speed Carbon: Own the City" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>EA Games</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>05/29/09</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Pac-Mania" URL="/zeebo/991449-pac-mania">
		<Description>You know Pac-Man, that world-famous, dot-munchin', maze-runnin' yella fella who's full of fun and frenzy. Now you can play Pac-Man like you've never played before - in spectacular 3-D! In Pac-Mania, everything on the screen comes alive! The lovable ghosts glide through the air. Dots and energizer pellets hang in midair. Pac-Man gets a new power: He can jump up and over ghosts! There's also a Pac Booster feature that lets you move Pac-Man at superspeed. You'll love the new challenging mazes - they come in so many mind-boggling shapes, they'll turn you into a certified Pac-Maniac!</Description>
		<UserRating>3.50 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Easy</Difficulty>
		<Length>4 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Namco Bandai Games</Developer>
		<Franchise>Pac-Man</Franchise>
		<Genre>Action &gt; Arcade</Genre>
		<Release name="Pac-Mania" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Namco Bandai Games</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>06/16/09</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Peggle" URL="/zeebo/991491-peggle">
		<Description>Do you have what it takes to be a Peggle Master? Take your best shot in the new version of Peggle, exclusively for Xbox LIVE Arcade! Shoot and clear all the orange pegs to achieve Extreme Fever. Conquer 55 wild levels as 10 outlandish Masters help you rise to Peggle greatness. Wield 10 Magic Powers in Adventure mode and you're just getting started!

Put your skills to the test with 75 challenges as you rack up bonus points and style shots you'll smile about for weeks. Face off against friends, the computer or anyone online in Duel mode. Or, compete in live multiplayer action against up to four players in the Peg Party. Plus, you can earn 12 Xbox achievements and check out the Live Leaderboards to see where you rank worldwide!</Description>
		<Difficulty>Just Right</Difficulty>
		<Developer>Vega Mobile</Developer>
		<Franchise>Peggle</Franchise>
		<Genre>Puzzle &gt; Action</Genre>
		<Release name="Peggle" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>PopCap</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>03/09/10</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Powerboat Challenge" URL="/zeebo/611157-powerboat-challenge">
		<Description>Update 1.0.3 for OS 3.0 is live.
- - - - - - - - - -
iphonegamenetwork 4.5/5:
"Powerboat Challenge is an excellent step towards actually getting PSP-quality games on your iPhone, and is by far the best iPhone racing game out there!"

Pimp up your powerboat and go full throttle to compete against cool dudes and hot chicks in high-speed racing on twisted rivers. Prove your drive style and pass the buoys correctly along the course to fill up your boost bar and to unlock additional tuning options. With the prize money you win in the races you can upgrade your boat with bigger engines, chip tuning, fatter turbos, spoilers and such.

- Four cool characters with stylish racing boats to choose from 
- Four different venues with lots of competitions 
- Different disciplines such as classic lap racing, time qualifications and the thrilling elimination competition 
- In-game shop with lots of tuning options for your powerboat 
- Several hours of exciting game play, easy to learn, hard to master 

Search for fishlabsgame on YouTube to check out the in-game trailer.</Description>
		<Developer>Fishlabs</Developer>
		<Genre>Racing &gt; Arcade &gt; Other</Genre>
		<Release name="Powerboat Challenge" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Fishlabs</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>10/12/10</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Prey Evil" URL="/zeebo/991379-prey-evil">
		<Description>Prey Evil is an Action game, developed by 3D Realms and published by Machineworks Northwest,  which was released in South America in 2009.</Description>
		<Developer>3D Realms</Developer>
		<Franchise>Prey</Franchise>
		<Genre>Action &gt; Shooter &gt; First-Person &gt; Arcade</Genre>
		<Release name="Prey Evil" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Machineworks Northwest</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>05/29/09</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Quake" URL="/zeebo/991378-quake">
		<Description>From the creators of DOOM and DOOM II comes the most intense, technologically advanced 3-D experience ever captured on CD ROM. Features free and fluid motion, ambient sound and lighting, and unmatched multi-player capabilities.</Description>
		<UserRating>2.75 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Unforgiving</Difficulty>
		<Length>2 hours</Length>
		<Developer>id Software</Developer>
		<Franchise>Quake</Franchise>
		<Genre>Action &gt; Shooter &gt; First-Person &gt; Arcade</Genre>
		<Release name="Quake" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>id Software</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>05/29/09</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Quake II" URL="/zeebo/991377-quake-ii">
		<Description>Shortly after landing on an alien surface, you learn that hundreds of your men have been reduced to just a few. Now you must fight your way through heavily fortified military installations, lower the city's defenses and shut down the enemy's war machine. Only then will the fate of humanity be known.</Description>
		<UserRating>4.17 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Unforgiving</Difficulty>
		<Length>8 hours</Length>
		<Developer>id Software</Developer>
		<Franchise>Quake</Franchise>
		<Genre>Action &gt; Shooter &gt; First-Person &gt; Arcade</Genre>
		<Release name="Quake II" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>id Software</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>05/29/09</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Raging Thunder II" URL="/zeebo/620215-raging-thunder-ii">
		<Description>Raging Thunder II is a Racing game, developed by Pixelbite and published by Polarbit,  which was released in South America in 2010.</Description>
		<Developer>Pixelbite</Developer>
		<Genre>Racing &gt; Arcade &gt; Automobile</Genre>
		<Release name="Raging Thunder II" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Polarbit</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>12/07/10</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Rally Master Pro" URL="/zeebo/996089-rally-master-pro">
		<Description>Rally Master Pro is a Racing game, developed and published by Fishlabs,  which was released in South America in 2009.</Description>
		<UserRating>3.00 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Simple</Difficulty>
		<Length>4 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Fishlabs</Developer>
		<Genre>Racing &gt; Arcade &gt; Automobile</Genre>
		<Release name="Rally Master Pro" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Fishlabs</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>12/21/09</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Resident Evil 4: Zeebo Edition" URL="/zeebo/991450-resident-evil-4-zeebo-edition">
		<Description>Resident Evil 4 marks a new chapter in the Resident Evil series. You'll rejoin Leon S. Kennedy six years after his first mission as a rookie cop from Resident Evil 2. Now a US agent, Leon is on a top secret mission to investigate the disappearance of the president's daughter. As Leon, you must make your way to a mysterious location in Europe, where new enemies await. Take them down by using enhanced aim-and-shoot features and a new action button.</Description>
		<UserRating>2.86 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Just Right</Difficulty>
		<Length>8 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Capcom</Developer>
		<Franchise>Resident Evil</Franchise>
		<Genre>Action Adventure &gt; Survival</Genre>
		<Release name="Resident Evil 4: Zeebo Edition" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Capcom</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>08/11/09</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Ridge Racer" URL="/zeebo/991451-ridge-racer">
		<Description>Ridge Racer is a Racing game, developed and published by Namco Bandai Games,  which was released in South America in 2009.</Description>
		<Developer>Namco Bandai Games</Developer>
		<Franchise>Ridge Racer</Franchise>
		<Genre>Racing &gt; Arcade &gt; Automobile</Genre>
		<Release name="Ridge Racer" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Namco Bandai Games</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>08/11/09</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="SpinMaster" URL="/zeebo/996105-spinmaster">
		<Description>SpinMaster is an Action game, developed by Data East and published by G-mode,  which was released in South America in 2010.</Description>
		<Developer>Data East</Developer>
		<Genre>Action &gt; Platformer &gt; 2D</Genre>
		<Release name="SpinMaster" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>G-mode</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>04/16/10</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Street Fighter Alpha" URL="/zeebo/991452-street-fighter-alpha">
		<Description>Intense. Brutal. Combat. The world has never encountered such a powerful collection of fighters in one tournament. Until now... Every Warrior's Dream - the most devastating Street Fighters of all time assemble to battle in one ultimate contest. Armed with an arsenal of new martial art moves, super combos and deadly secrets, the legendary competitors Ryu, Chun-Li, Ken and Sagat collide with a lethal new combination of fierce opponents. Infamous aggressors - Charlie, Sodom, Birdie and Guy show they play for keeps when they battle on the street. The new contenders Rose and Adon draw powers of the soul and nature to annihilate opponents and secure fame, power and prestige. The most extreme one-on-one warfare ever!</Description>
		<Developer>Capcom</Developer>
		<Franchise>Street Fighter Alpha</Franchise>
		<Genre>Action &gt; Fighting &gt; 2D</Genre>
		<Release name="Street Fighter Alpha" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Capcom</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>2009</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Street Hoop" URL="/zeebo/996106-street-hoop">
		<Description>Which team is the best at 3-on-3? Choose from ten countries to find out. Shots vary according to the shooting distance. Fake dunk, aloof - a variety of techniques to choose from! Speedy! Powerful! Move your body to hip hoppin' rap music. When the power guage reaches its max, Super Dunk sparks!</Description>
		<UserRating>4.75 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Just Right</Difficulty>
		<Length>0.8 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Data East</Developer>
		<Genre>Sports &gt; Team &gt; Basketball &gt; Sim</Genre>
		<Release name="Street Hoop" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>G-mode</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>04/16/10</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Super Burger Time" URL="/zeebo/996107-super-burger-time">
		<Description>Super Burger Time is an Action game, developed by Data East and published by G-mode,  which was released in South America in 2010.</Description>
		<Developer>Data East</Developer>
		<Franchise>BurgerTime</Franchise>
		<Genre>Action &gt; Platformer &gt; 2D</Genre>
		<Release name="Super Burger Time" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>G-mode</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>04/16/10</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Tekken 2" URL="/zeebo/991453-tekken-2">
		<Description>Tekken 2 is an Action game, developed and published by Namco Bandai Games,  which was released in South America in 2009.</Description>
		<UserRating>4.50 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Just Right</Difficulty>
		<Length>3 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Namco Bandai Games</Developer>
		<Franchise>Tekken</Franchise>
		<Genre>Action &gt; Fighting &gt; 3D</Genre>
		<Release name="Tekken 2" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Namco Bandai Games</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>10/08/09</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Tork and Kral: A Prehistorik Adventure" URL="/zeebo/620214-tork-and-kral-a-prehistorik-adventure">
		<Description>Tork and Kral: A Prehistorik Adventure is an Action game, developed and published by Vega Mobile,  which was released in South America in 2010.</Description>
		<Developer>Vega Mobile</Developer>
		<Genre>Action &gt; Platformer &gt; 2D</Genre>
		<Release name="Tork and Kral: A Prehistorik Adventure" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Vega Mobile</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>11/16/10</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Toy Raid" URL="/zeebo/996090-toy-raid">
		<Description>"the original iPod's Parachute game is back"
Adam Immersive

"Like Sabotage But Better"
Adam


******************************************************
Toy Raid here! Relive your favorite toy memories by challenging some of the most epic toy battles from your childhood in over 50 action-filled levels. With its bright and colorful toy styled visuals and toy inspired audio, Toy Raid has been called one of the most exciting iPhone shooting games. Grab your iPhone or iPod and battle wave-upon-wave of relentless enemies in Toy Raid. Toy Raid feature and endless mania of Toy Enemies attacking you.

Toy Raid Is and Exciting casual fun arcade game with simple and fun controls that can be just picked up and played easily by all.

******************************************************
PRESS REVIEWS:
******************************************************
"Toy Raid" Is Simple Shooter Fun"
www.Toucharcade.com 

"Open Fire with Toy Raid!"
www.iphoneincanada.ca

"the original iPod's Parachute game is back"
Adam Immersive

"A seemingly endless stream of planes to shoot down"
www.mobileegamefaqs.com

Toy Raid was featured on the Tom Green Show In Webovision 
www.TomGreen.com

See the episode Featuring Toy Raid here.
http://www.tomgreen.com/?video=1424

*****************************************************
HOW TO PLAY:
*****************************************************
-Destroy all the Parachutes by shooting them
-Touch controls swipe left or right to move cannon
-Tilt Controls tilt phone left or right to move cannon
-Shake Control Unique feature shaking the phone destroys all enemies with Nuke.

Relive the epic Toy battles of your childhood in high resolution with realistic Toy's, massive explosions, and heart-pounding SFX &amp; Action!  Watch plane wreckage burst into flames! Hear enemy paratroopers scream as they plummet to their doom!
Grab every special weapon and nuke to keep your anti-air cannon alive through 50+ levels of mayhem as helicopters, planes, jets, zeppelins, UFOs, and paratroopers attempt to bomb your base into oblivion!
Control your aim by touch, or use the tilt option to move the cannon with just a flick of the wrist.  Shake to unleash a Nuke on a screen full of unsuspecting enemies.
Toy Raidâs intense action will satisfy your craving for that classic arcade feel!

The Toy Raid game is a fusion of new and old that's fun for all.

*********************************************************


*********************************************************
Gameplay Tips:
*********************************************************
-Destroy all Biplanes and get power ups
-Destroy Parachutes when they are close to landing
-Conserve Nukes for when you have a lot of enemies

*********************************************************
Gameplay Videos:
*********************************************************
1. Http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xNn03aEBRog
2. Http://www.tinyurl.com/ToyRaid
3. Http://www.tinyurl.com/Toyraid2

*******************************************************
Game Features:
*******************************************************
 Over 50 levels
 6 Power-ups to choose from
 Play with Tilt or Touch Controls
 Languages:
          English 
          Spanish



Keyword:
Toyraid,Mecho wars,camera zoom</Description>
		<Developer>Flying Tiger Development</Developer>
		<Genre>Action &gt; Shooter &gt; Shoot-'Em-Up &gt; Vertical</Genre>
		<Release name="Toy Raid" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Flying Tiger Development</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>03/09/10</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Ultimate Chess 3D" URL="/zeebo/991454-ultimate-chess-3d">
		<Description>Ultimate Chess 3D is a Miscellaneous game, developed and published by Glu Mobile,  which was released in South America in 2009.</Description>
		<Developer>Glu Mobile</Developer>
		<Genre>Miscellaneous &gt; Board / Card Game</Genre>
		<Release name="Ultimate Chess 3D" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Glu Mobile</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>12/09/09</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Um Jogo de Ovos" URL="/zeebo/611175-um-jogo-de-ovos">
		<Description>Um Jogo de Ovos is an Action game, developed and published by Fabrication Games,  which was released in South America in 2010.</Description>
		<Developer>Fabrication Games</Developer>
		<Genre>Action &gt; Platformer &gt; 2D</Genre>
		<Release name="Um Jogo de Ovos" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Fabrication Games</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>08/25/10</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Wizard Fire" URL="/zeebo/996108-wizard-fire">
		<Description>Wizard Fire is an Action game, developed by Data East and published by G-mode,  which was released in South America in 2010.</Description>
		<Developer>Data East</Developer>
		<Genre>Action &gt; Beat-'Em-Up &gt; 2D</Genre>
		<Release name="Wizard Fire" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>G-mode</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>04/16/10</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Zeebo" URL="/zeebo/991376-zeebo">
		<Description>Zeebo is a Hardware game, developed and published by Zeebo Inc.,  which was released in South America in 2009.</Description>
		<UserRating>2.30 / 5</UserRating>
		<Developer>Zeebo Inc.</Developer>
		<Genre>Hardware &gt; Console</Genre>
		<Release name="Zeebo" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Zeebo Inc.</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode> </ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>05/29/09</ReleaseDate>
			<ReleaseImages>
				<Image>Zeebo (SA)-146638_front.jpg</Image>
				<Image>Zeebo (SA)-146638_back.jpg</Image>
			</ReleaseImages>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Zeebo Extreme: Baja" URL="/zeebo/991455-zeebo-extreme-baja">
		<Description>Zeebo Extreme: Baja is a Racing game, developed and published by Tec Toy,  which was released in South America in 2009.</Description>
		<UserRating>0.50 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Simple</Difficulty>
		<Length>0.5 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Tec Toy</Developer>
		<Genre>Racing &gt; Arcade &gt; Automobile</Genre>
		<Release name="Zeebo Extreme: Baja" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Tec Toy</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>10/31/09</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Zeebo Extreme: Boia Cross" URL="/zeebo/991456-zeebo-extreme-boia-cross">
		<Description>Zeebo Extreme: Boia Cross is a Racing game, developed and published by Tec Toy,  which was released in South America in 2009.</Description>
		<Developer>Tec Toy</Developer>
		<Genre>Racing &gt; Arcade &gt; Automobile</Genre>
		<Release name="Zeebo Extreme: Boia Cross" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Tec Toy</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>12/21/09</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Zeebo Extreme: Corrida Aerea" URL="/zeebo/991457-zeebo-extreme-corrida-aerea">
		<Description>Zeebo Extreme: Corrida Aerea is a Racing game, developed and published by Tec Toy,  which was released in South America in 2009.</Description>
		<UserRating>2.00 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Simple</Difficulty>
		<Length>2 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Tec Toy</Developer>
		<Genre>Racing &gt; Arcade &gt; Automobile</Genre>
		<Release name="Zeebo Extreme: Corrida Aerea" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Tec Toy</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>09/29/09</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Zeebo Extreme: Jetboard" URL="/zeebo/991458-zeebo-extreme-jetboard">
		<Description>Zeebo Extreme: Jetboard is a Racing game, developed and published by Tec Toy,  which was released in South America in 2009.</Description>
		<UserRating>1.00 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Simple</Difficulty>
		<Length>1 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Tec Toy</Developer>
		<Genre>Racing &gt; Arcade &gt; Automobile</Genre>
		<Release name="Zeebo Extreme: Jetboard" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Tec Toy</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>12/21/09</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Zeebo Extreme: Rolima" URL="/zeebo/991459-zeebo-extreme-rolima">
		<Description>Zeebo Extreme: Rolima is a Racing game, developed and published by Tec Toy,  which was released in South America in 2009.</Description>
		<UserRating>2.50 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Simple</Difficulty>
		<Length>4 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Tec Toy</Developer>
		<Genre>Racing &gt; Arcade &gt; Automobile</Genre>
		<Release name="Zeebo Extreme: Rolima" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Tec Toy</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>08/15/09</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Zeebo F. C. Super League" URL="/zeebo/619335-zeebo-f-c-super-league">
		<Description>Zeebo F. C. Super League is a Sports game, developed and published by Zeebo Inc.,  which was released in South America in 2010.</Description>
		<Developer>Zeebo Inc.</Developer>
		<Genre>Sports &gt; Team &gt; Football &gt; Arcade</Genre>
		<Release name="Zeebo F. C. Super League" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Zeebo Inc.</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>12/22/10</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Zeebo F.C. Foot Camp" URL="/zeebo/620221-zeebo-fc-foot-camp">
		<Description>Zeebo F.C. Foot Camp is a Sports game, developed and published by Zeebo Inc.,  which was released in South America in 2010.</Description>
		<Developer>Zeebo Inc.</Developer>
		<Genre>Sports &gt; General</Genre>
		<Release name="Zeebo F.C. Foot Camp" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Zeebo Inc.</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>06/02/10</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Zeebo Family Pack" URL="/zeebo/991460-zeebo-family-pack">
		<Description>Zeebo Family Pack is a Miscellaneous game, developed and published by Tec Toy,  which was released in South America in 2009.</Description>
		<Developer>Tec Toy</Developer>
		<Genre>Miscellaneous &gt; Party / Minigame</Genre>
		<Release name="Zeebo Family Pack" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Tec Toy</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>09/29/09</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Zenonia" URL="/zeebo/991461-zenonia">
		<Description>THE RETURN OF CLASSIC ACTION RPGAWARDS: Best Adventure/RPG Game from The Pocket Gamer Awards 2010: iPhoneBest Game of 2009 by Apple's Rewind 2009Best RPG Game of 2009 by IGNBest Role Playing iPod Touch and iPhone Game of 2009 by Touch ArcadeTop 10 iPhone Games of 2009 by AppGamerBest RPG 2009 by TouchGenEditor's Choice Award by IGNZENONIA, has become the frontrunner of the Classic RPG Genre in App Store. It ensures vast amounts of adventure, hours of playing time, hundreds of items, skill and quest which follows an epic storyline.---------------------CRITICS SAYRanked No.1 iPhone RPG - IGN Game Reviews (9/10)“ZENONIA harkens back to Link to the Past, the bestselling 16-bit chapter in the long-running Zelda franchise, but with graphics that are much closer to Phantom Hourglass for the Nintendo DS.”- IGN EDITOR'S CHOICE AWARD (9/10)“If you've been looking for something on the App Store that compares to the classic 16-bit RPG's from days of yore, ZENONIA may just be what you've been searching for. GAMEVIL seems to have designed this game specifically for gamers clamoring for a classic action RPG experience.” - Touch Arcade“The game looks like a souped-up version of Legend of Zelda: A Link To the Past for the SNES, with more animation, brighter colors, and more complex game play such as thousands of weapons and items to collect and a full Diablo-like skill tree.” - SlideToPlay---------------------FEATURESNUMEROUS QUESTS FOLLOWING AN EPIC STORYLINEExtensive playing time of over 40 hours to conquer the main and side questsCREATE YOUR OWN CHARACTERChoose your hero from 3 different classes; warrior, paladin and assassin. Customize your attributes accordinglyHUNDREDS OF ITEMSCollect items from 5 different classes(normal, magic, rare, unique and epic) to enchant or combine them for upgradesSTUNNING EFFECTS AND GRAPHICSAnime style characters and graphics, along with various stylish skill effectsINNOVATIVE REAL LIFE SYSTEMDay/night cycle, hunger/weight system and good/evil storyline path to choose from---------------------OTHER GAMEVIL GAMES Air Penguin Baseball Superstars® II Baseball Superstars® 2010 HD Boom It Up! Chalk n' Talk DESTINIA HYBRID: Eternal WhisperHYBRID 2: Saga of Nostalgia ILLUSIA KAMI RETRO KAMI RETRO HD LAST WARNOM: Billion Year Timequest NOM 5Skipping Stone Soccer Superstars® 2011 Pro VANQUISH: The Oath of Brothers ZENONIA® 3 --------------------- NEWS &amp; EVENTS Website http://www.gamevil.com Facebook http://facebook.com/gamevil Twitter http://twitter.com/gamevil YouTube http://youtube.com/gamevil</Description>
		<UserRating>4.50 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Tough</Difficulty>
		<Length>40 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Gamevil</Developer>
		<Franchise>Zenonia</Franchise>
		<Genre>Role-Playing &gt; Action RPG</Genre>
		<Release name="Zenonia" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>Gamevil</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>10/31/09</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zeebo" name="Zuma's Revenge!" URL="/zeebo/646764-zumas-revenge">
		<Description>Experience new levels of ball-blasting action! Leap in and conquer 69 levels of Adventure mode. Discover four new Spirit Animals (at least one of them is a monkey!) and harness their abilities to power up your game. Dive in to the high-stakes Iron Frog mode: 10 levels, one frog. Can you make it out alive? Battle all 8 tiki bosses in the fast-paced Boss Rush. Enter the Weekly Challenge and compete for high score on a new level every week.</Description>
		<UserRating>4.17 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Just Right</Difficulty>
		<Length>6 hours</Length>
		<Developer>PopCap</Developer>
		<Franchise>Zuma</Franchise>
		<Genre>Puzzle &gt; Action</Genre>
		<Release name="Zuma's Revenge!" region="SA">
			<ReleasePublisher>PopCap</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>07/14/10</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
</softwarelist>
