<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<softwarelist>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Acedior" URL="/zod/953020-acedior">
		<Description>On April 22th, 1365, the king of France sent a military squad around the area of the Bourget Lake in Savoy to get rid of some goups of gypsies that were roaming the countryside and terrorizing the local villagers with their shady reputation. The soldiers decided to rest for the night in the Chatelombre monastery, but when they got there they discovered that it had been abandoned.

The evening's dinner was ready and the table was set, but they couldn't find any sign of the 16 monks that were supposed to live there.

This game is based on the true story of the disappearance of the Chamberlombre monks, but the interpretation of events is fictional...

Enter the mysterious monastery of Chatelombre and become brother Baptiste, a monk trying to understand the horrible curse that has fallen on the monastery.

Acedior is a point and click adventure for the Tapwave Zodiac that features beautiful computer generated graphics.</Description>
		<UserRating>2.50 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Tough</Difficulty>
		<Length>1 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Fade Team</Developer>
		<Genre>Adventure &gt; General</Genre>
		<Release name="Acedior" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Fade Team</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode> </ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>2004</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Altered Beast" URL="/zod/921381-altered-beast">
		<Description>You've been recruited by Zeus to rescue Athena, and you'll have to make your way through five levels of the evil Underworld to save her. Luckily, you have the ability to transform into savage beasts that make you even more powerful than in your human form. Whether you're the Werewolf, the Weredragon, or the Weretiger, you'll gain special abilities as each beast that will make you an unstoppable machine. Zeus is counting on you.don't let him down.</Description>
		<UserRating>2.83 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Tough</Difficulty>
		<Length>12 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Sega</Developer>
		<Franchise>Altered Beast</Franchise>
		<Genre>Action &gt; Beat-'Em-Up &gt; 2D</Genre>
		<Release name="Altered Beast" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Sega</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode> </ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>2004</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="AnotherBall" URL="/zod/921386-anotherball">
		<Description>A modern version of the classic 80's game Arkanoid, this colorful, exciting game will have you glued to blasting your way through many different kinds of blocks (glass, steel, explosive etc.) to earn points and go for higher scores. Play through multiple levels and work to earn bonuses. But be careful, there might be life-threatening obstacles just around the corner!</Description>
		<UserRating>3.80 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Tough</Difficulty>
		<Length>11.2 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Paragon Software</Developer>
		<Genre>Puzzle &gt; General</Genre>
		<Release name="AnotherBall" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Paragon Software</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode> </ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>2004</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Atari Retro" URL="/zod/921499-atari-retro">
		<Description>Atari Retro pitches you against challenge after challenge on your quest to conquer a series of strange worlds. Match wits with your console as you struggle to expand your Atari Retro. Featuring beautifully rendered 3D isometric graphics and a haunting audio-visual atmosphere; this strategic puzzle game might well turn out to be your next obsession.

A compilation of seven groundbreaking Atari games optimized for the Zodiac. Atari Retro includes some of the most beloved Atari classics - AdventureT, Asteroids®, Breakout®, Centipede®, Missile Command®, Pong®, and Yar's Revenge®.</Description>
		<UserRating>4.33 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Just Right</Difficulty>
		<Length>6.7 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Atari</Developer>
		<Genre>Miscellaneous &gt; Compilation</Genre>
		<Release name="Atari Retro" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Atari</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>2004</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Avalanche" URL="/zod/953503-avalanche">
		<Description>Avalanche is a Puzzle game, developed by Digital Eclipse and published by Backbone Entertainment,  which was released in 2004.</Description>
		<UserRating>4.63 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Easy</Difficulty>
		<Length>14 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Digital Eclipse</Developer>
		<Genre>Puzzle &gt; General</Genre>
		<Release name="Avalanche" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Backbone Entertainment</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>Q4 2004</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Billiards 3D" URL="/zod/953410-billiards-3d">
		<Description>Choose from 6 different game options. Customize your table type, ball size and table preferences. Even choose the color of the felt. Great digital sound effects. A wide range of games, geometric settings, real life physics modeling and "videotape" review of your last shot will allow you to sharpen your skills enough to get you ready to take on the local pool shark.</Description>
		<UserRating>3.92 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Easy</Difficulty>
		<Length>14.5 hours</Length>
		<Developer>MegaSoft 2000</Developer>
		<Genre>Sports &gt; Individual &gt; Other</Genre>
		<Release name="Billiards 3D" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>MegaSoft 2000</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode> </ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>2004</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Bubble Shooter 2" URL="/zod/921380-bubble-shooter-2">
		<Description>A cool game with simple rules and great wealth of combinations and various strategies. With high resolution graphics as well as new game modes (Strategy, Sniper, Arcade and Marathon), new levels (Easy Ride, Novice, Expert and Master), music and sound effects, this special edition for Zodiac is a lot of fun! Beware, it is very addictive.</Description>
		<UserRating>3.92 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Easy</Difficulty>
		<Length>14.1 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Absolutist Ltd</Developer>
		<Genre>Puzzle &gt; General</Genre>
		<Release name="Bubble Shooter 2" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Absolutist Ltd</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode> </ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>2004</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Colony" URL="/zod/953415-colony">
		<Description>Colony pitches you against challenge after challenge on your quest to conquer a series of strange worlds. Match wits with your console as you struggle to expand your colony. Featuring beautifully rendered 3D isometric graphics and a haunting audio-visual atmosphere; this strategic puzzle game might well turn out to be your next obsession.</Description>
		<UserRating>4.25 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Tough</Difficulty>
		<Length>65 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Rusty Axe Games</Developer>
		<Genre>Strategy &gt; General</Genre>
		<Release name="Colony" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Rusty Axe Games</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>2004</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Crossword Puzzles" URL="/zod/953021-crossword-puzzles">
		<Description>Solve crossword puzzles anywhere, at any time! Download new puzzles wirelessly or during a HotSync® operation. Quickly view mistakes, or restart a puzzle. Manage all your puzzles, or move them to a memory card.</Description>
		<UserRating>4.00 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Easy</Difficulty>
		<Length>30.1 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Stand Alone, Inc.</Developer>
		<Genre>Puzzle &gt; General</Genre>
		<Release name="Crossword Puzzles" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Stand Alone, Inc.</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode> </ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>2004</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Daedalus 3D - The Labyrinth" URL="/zod/953022-daedalus-3d-the-labyrinth">
		<Description>Full 3D First Person Shooter action game the Tapwave Zodiac - make your way through 23 beautiful and detailed levels, vanquishing foes with a selection of 4 different weapons and finding your way through the maze. Enjoy 3 difficulty modes of challenge!</Description>
		<UserRating>3.00 / 5</UserRating>
		<Developer>Safoa.net</Developer>
		<Genre>Action &gt; Shooter &gt; First-Person &gt; Arcade</Genre>
		<Release name="Daedalus 3D - The Labyrinth" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Safoa.net</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode> </ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>2004</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Doom II" URL="/zod/920944-doom-ii">
		<Description>The entire forces of the netherworld have overrun the Earth. To save her, you must descend into the stygian depths of HELL itself!

Use overwhelming firepower to battle the fiercest, nastiest, and deadliest demons and monsters ever conceived. Survive mind-blowing explosions and the bloodiest, most awesome blast fest ever!</Description>
		<UserRating>2.31 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Just Right</Difficulty>
		<Length>9 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Machineworks Northwest</Developer>
		<Franchise>Doom</Franchise>
		<Genre>Action &gt; Shooter &gt; First-Person &gt; Arcade</Genre>
		<Release name="Doom II" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>id Software</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode> </ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>05/11/04</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Dreamway" URL="/zod/921379-dreamway">
		<Description>Buzz through a gang of opponents to leave everyone behind. Three challenging game modes: Single Race to perfect your driving skills; The Cup - new cars and tracks available as you progress; and Knockout - the last one in the lap gets eliminated. Tough game play centered around the action on the road: smart AI opponents of varying tech specs, fancy weapons and surprising bonuses.</Description>
		<UserRating>3.75 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Tough</Difficulty>
		<Length>1 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Handy Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
		<Genre>Racing &gt; Arcade &gt; Automobile</Genre>
		<Release name="Dreamway" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Handy Entertainment, Inc.</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode> </ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>2004</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Duke Nukem Mobile" URL="/zod/921376-duke-nukem-mobile">
		<Description>Aliens are invading your Zodiac -- who ya gonna call: Duke Nukem!
The king of action heroes, Duke Nukem is bringing his kick-butt style of alien extermination to the world of Tapwave. One man versus 1000 aliens -- it's hardly fair! But don't expect Duke to show pity as he blasts each one into quivering goo.</Description>
		<UserRating>4.00 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Tough</Difficulty>
		<Length>4.4 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Machineworks Northwest</Developer>
		<Franchise>Duke Nukem</Franchise>
		<Genre>Action &gt; Shooter &gt; First-Person &gt; Arcade</Genre>
		<Release name="Duke Nukem Mobile" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>3D Realms</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>06/29/04</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Firefly" URL="/zod/921382-firefly">
		<Description>Explore the mazes of a garden, beehive, castle, and laboratory gathering eggs and avoiding the not-so-friendly bugs of the world. Firefly's absorbing game play can be enhanced by adjusting speed and difficulty. Enjoy hours of additional fun using the random maze generator to create larger and more difficult mazes.</Description>
		<UserRating>4.00 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Simple</Difficulty>
		<Length>1 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Extreme AI, Inc.</Developer>
		<Genre>Puzzle &gt; General</Genre>
		<Release name="Firefly" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Extreme AI, Inc.</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>2004</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="FireHammer" URL="/zod/953411-firehammer">
		<Description>Just one ship against an invading alien armada - FireHammer brings the traditional vertical shoot 'em up experience to the Zodiac! Survival is a matter of lightning-fast reflexes as you guide your space fighter through swarms of enemy projectiles and take on the slowly advancing fleet of enemy battleships.

Collect power-ups to improve your weapons, and activate the experimental super weapon to help you out of tight spots. FireHammer also features a bonus chain score multiplier system, which allows the truly hardcore pilots to duke it out on the online ranking list.</Description>
		<UserRating>4.00 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Tough</Difficulty>
		<Length>20 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Fathammer</Developer>
		<Genre>Action &gt; General</Genre>
		<Release name="FireHammer" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Fathammer</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode> </ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>2004</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Fish Tycoon" URL="/zod/953504-fish-tycoon">
		<Description>Fish Tycoon is a fish-breeding sim with an entrepreneurial twist. Raise your fish in real-time virtual aquariums then crossbreed them however you see fit to create all-new, super unique breeds. Open your fish store and sell your fish to raise money for supplies, medicine, and special chemicals while researching new technologies or investing in advertising.</Description>
		<UserRating>4.50 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Easy</Difficulty>
		<Length>29.2 hours</Length>
		<Developer>LDW</Developer>
		<Genre>Strategy &gt; Management &gt; Business / Tycoon</Genre>
		<Release name="Fish Tycoon" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>LDW</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>Q4 2004</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Frutakia" URL="/zod/953024-frutakia">
		<Description>A new fun and addicting puzzle game from the makers of PaintBall that will suck you in and won't let you go! Frutakia takes the idea of casino slot machines and turns it into an original puzzle game.</Description>
		<UserRating>3.00 / 5</UserRating>
		<Developer>Crazysoft</Developer>
		<Genre>Puzzle &gt; General</Genre>
		<Release name="Frutakia" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Crazysoft</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode> </ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>2004</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Galactic Realms" URL="/zod/921384-galactic-realms">
		<Description>With the recent expansion into space, several factions have continued their struggle for dominance in the dark void. The United Nations has set up a council to govern and monitor the new colonies, but there are those who prefer only chaos. With the new rebel threat, the UN council has no choice but to declare war and to start building their own battleships to eliminate the rebel menace. You have been selected to command the UN fleet, but the rebels will prove to be a formidable opponent, and a new unknown threat has yet to be unveiled.</Description>
		<UserRating>4.30 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Just Right</Difficulty>
		<Length>6.4 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Crimson Fire</Developer>
		<Genre>Strategy &gt; Real-Time &gt; General</Genre>
		<Release name="Galactic Realms" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Crimson Fire</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode> </ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>2004</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Gloop Zero" URL="/zod/953505-gloop-zero">
		<Description>Gloop Zero is a Puzzle game, developed and published by Aeon Flame,  which was released in 2004.</Description>
		<UserRating>2.50 / 5</UserRating>
		<Developer>Aeon Flame</Developer>
		<Genre>Puzzle &gt; Action</Genre>
		<Release name="Gloop Zero" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Aeon Flame</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>Q4 2004</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Golden Axe" URL="/zod/921664-golden-axe">
		<Description>In GOLDEN AXE, it's up to you to exact revenge and rid the world of one of the most vile and heinous beings to ever walk the planet. As either Gilius Thunderhead or Tyris Flare, you'll journey through a world full of dragons, undead skeletons, and brutal barbarians as you seek out Death Adder. Utilize your impressive axe skills or your mastery of magic to destroy any foe that dares to challenge you, and enlist the help of several animal friends that will make you an unstoppable force</Description>
		<UserRating>3.88 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Tough</Difficulty>
		<Length>3.3 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Lavastorm</Developer>
		<Franchise>Golden Axe</Franchise>
		<Genre>Action &gt; Beat-'Em-Up &gt; 2D</Genre>
		<Release name="Golden Axe" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Sega</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode> </ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>01/01/04</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Green Myste, The" URL="/zod/921388-the-green-myste">
		<Description>Your character will gain experience and power as the mysteries of Sanctis, the Grim, and the Green Myste are unraveled. You will meet various adventurers whom you may invite to join you, adding to the skill set and power of your party-all of which will be helpful as you battle hundreds of monsters and defeat countless tricks and traps spread throughout the adventure.

The game employs familiar character role-playing mechanics: gaining experience to increase power, enlisting a party of adventurers, and maintaining an inventory of many different kinds of items.

The Green Myste, a living, breathing world, more than four years in the making, is now yours to explore and enjoy.</Description>
		<UserRating>3.25 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Easy</Difficulty>
		<Length>20 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Rusty Axe Games</Developer>
		<Genre>Role-Playing &gt; Western-Style</Genre>
		<Release name="The Green Myste" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Rusty Axe Games</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode> </ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>2004</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="GTS Racing Challenge" URL="/zod/953506-gts-racing-challenge">
		<Description>GTS Racing Challenge is a Racing game, developed by OutLook Entertainment and published by Pazzazz Games,  which was released in 2004.</Description>
		<UserRating>4.42 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Tough</Difficulty>
		<Length>10.4 hours</Length>
		<Developer>OutLook Entertainment</Developer>
		<Genre>Racing &gt; Simulation &gt; Automobile</Genre>
		<Release name="GTS Racing Challenge" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Pazzazz Games</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode> </ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>Q4 2004</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Hockey Rage 2005" URL="/zod/924219-hockey-rage-2005">
		<Description>Hockey Rage 2005 is a Sports game, developed and published by Fathammer,  which was released in 2004.</Description>
		<UserRating>3.88 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Tough</Difficulty>
		<Length>9.3 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Fathammer</Developer>
		<Genre>Sports &gt; Team &gt; Ice Hockey &gt; Arcade</Genre>
		<Release name="Hockey Rage 2005" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Fathammer</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>Q4 2004</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Interstellar Flames" URL="/zod/921385-interstellar-flames">
		<Description>A vast horde of alien battleships is approaching our solar system. Due to maintenance problems only one fighter craft is ready to defend the planet. Fly dangerous missions against huge battlecruisers, dogfight with enemy fighters in asteroid fields and destroy the alien fleet before it enslaves Earth. Can you face them alone?

Interstellar Flames is an intense action game featuring a groundbreaking 3D engine.</Description>
		<UserRating>3.25 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Just Right</Difficulty>
		<Length>2 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Xen Games</Developer>
		<Genre>Action &gt; Shooter &gt; First-Person &gt; Arcade</Genre>
		<Release name="Interstellar Flames" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Xen Games</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>2004</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Kickoo's Breakout" URL="/zod/953025-kickoos-breakout">
		<Description>"A super-fast action game with stunning graphics and exciting challenges."

Your goal is simple - destroy all the bricks on the screen to get to the next level of play. It's getting there that can be the hard part. To get through all 36 levels of play you must prevent the ball from falling off the bottom part of the screen by moving the paddle underneath it. Here's the tricky part--this will cause the ball to bounce off in the direction of the bricks.

And, depending on the type of brick you destroy, some of them will release a "powerup" which you can catch with the paddle before it hits the bottom of the screen. These powerups can be helpful or harmful depending on the powerup and the situation. The catch is you will not know ahead of time.

If you do manage to avoid the nasty powerups, don't get too secure, because the monsters can still get you. They'll disrupt your game, modify your ball's trajectory and possibly cause you to lose a life.</Description>
		<UserRating>3.83 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Tough</Difficulty>
		<Length>7.3 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Kickoo</Developer>
		<Genre>Action &gt; General</Genre>
		<Release name="Kickoo's Breakout" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Kickoo</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode> </ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>2004</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Kickoo's TakTik" URL="/zod/953386-kickoos-taktik">
		<Description>Two players (Tak and Tik) compete against each other with armies of 18 pieces, with the goal of capturing the other's princess. The twist is that you cannot see your opponent's pieces and they cannot see yours. They are only revealed during a battle, so you won't know if you made the right choice until the battle takes place. And, you can check out the Graveyard to keep track of the pieces which have been eliminated.</Description>
		<UserRating>3.83 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Tough</Difficulty>
		<Length>12 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Kickoo</Developer>
		<Genre>Strategy &gt; General</Genre>
		<Release name="Kickoo's TakTik" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Kickoo</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode> </ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>2004</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Legacy" URL="/zod/921387-legacy">
		<Description>Challenge the minions of ultimate evil in this RPG tour-de-force from RedShift.

Cold steel and magic are your weapons as you command your party through incredibly graphic worlds and quests. An instant classic, this turn-based adventure is the perfect blend of strategy and action. Choose from 7 player types and an impressive array of weaponry, armor and enchantments. You'll need to bring your brain, because the puzzles are among the best ever. And the future will feature expansion packs for aspiring world designers.</Description>
		<UserRating>4.00 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Just Right</Difficulty>
		<Length>11.4 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Redshift</Developer>
		<Genre>Role-Playing &gt; Western-Style</Genre>
		<Release name="Legacy" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Redshift</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode> </ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>2004</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Madden NFL 2005" URL="/zod/925069-madden-nfl-2005">
		<Description>Now your Zodiac handheld can bring you the #1, authentic NFL simulation game, Madden NFL 2005 from EA SPORTS™. No other game brings you the realism or takes you closer to the experience of NFL football. Put your football skills to the test...anytime...anywhere!

Now in its 15th year, the best-selling, most critically acclaimed sports video game ever produced brings the authentic NFL stadium experience right on your Zodiac. Expertly recreated for mobile play with the latest 2005 player data and all the key features of the console version, EA's MADDEN NFL 2005 delivers unparalleled Zodiac play!</Description>
		<UserRating>4.40 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Easy</Difficulty>
		<Length>60 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Floodgate Entertainment</Developer>
		<Franchise>Madden Football</Franchise>
		<Genre>Sports &gt; Team &gt; Football &gt; Sim</Genre>
		<Release name="Madden NFL 2005" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Mobile Digital Media</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>November 2004</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="MegaBowling" URL="/zod/953412-megabowling">
		<Description>MegaBowling is a Sports game, developed and published by MegaSoft 2000,  which was released in 2004.</Description>
		<UserRating>4.40 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Just Right</Difficulty>
		<Length>48.4 hours</Length>
		<Developer>MegaSoft 2000</Developer>
		<Genre>Sports &gt; Individual &gt; Bowling</Genre>
		<Release name="MegaBowling" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>MegaSoft 2000</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode> </ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>2004</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="MicroQuad" URL="/zod/921378-microquad">
		<Description>Your mission is to race a quad bike around lots of different tracks and to attempt to move your way through the levels which are Baby Cup, Junior Cup, Pro Cup, Master Cup and Expert Cup. Each level includes 4 detailed and varied tracks (20 different race tracks in all) as well as your choice of 6 different quad bikes which have different specialties for Road, Off Road and Grip. You can even challenge your friends with multiplayer Bluetooth.

As you race your way through the courses, you will be able to unlock the 4 other categories and compete for the MicroQuad trophy!</Description>
		<UserRating>3.00 / 5</UserRating>
		<Developer>Viex Games</Developer>
		<Genre>Racing &gt; Simulation &gt; Automobile</Genre>
		<Release name="MicroQuad" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Viex Games</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode> </ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>2004</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="MTX Mototrax" URL="/zod/920951-mtx-mototrax">
		<Description>Push your bike to the limit.  MTX: Mototrax challenges race against seven other riders, perform outrageous gravity-defying stunts, and develop a career as an motocross athlete.  Play as or against any of the 12 top riders, earning money from contest wins and sponsorships to spend on customizing your attributes, upgrading your equipment, or buying access to new environments.  If you think you're the best, prove it in the online multiplayer mode, which includes over 25 tracks.  Accept the MTX: Mototrax challenge to become the ultimate motocross racer.</Description>
		<UserRating>4.40 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Tough</Difficulty>
		<Length>16 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Tapwave</Developer>
		<Genre>Racing &gt; Arcade &gt; Other</Genre>
		<Release name="MTX Mototrax" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Tapwave</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode> </ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>2004</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Neverwinter Nights" URL="/zod/920953-neverwinter-nights">
		<Description>A hideous evil has awoken in the Forgotten Realms.  Now, in order to save the inhabitants of the town of Neverwinter, you must uncover a sinister conspiracy, unmask your mysterious betrayer, and complete an epic struggle to defeat powerful forces of evil.  Neverwinter Nights combines Dungeon &amp; Dragons gameplay with a fantasy world filled with monsters, stories, weapons, and legends.  With the Neverwinter Toolset, you can design your own magic world, and then invite up to 64 of your friends to experience it.</Description>
		<Developer>Tapwave</Developer>
		<Franchise>Neverwinter Nights</Franchise>
		<Genre>Role-Playing &gt; Western-Style</Genre>
		<Release name="Neverwinter Nights" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Tapwave</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode> </ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>Canceled</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Orbz" URL="/zod/921984-orbz">
		<Description>Orbz is an action/arcade game set in colorful 3D environments. The object of the game is to shoot your orb at targets located throughout 14 distinct courses in a race to score the most points. Game play contains both intense action and also strategy in planning the best scoring shots. Power-ups, like the "Money Shot" and "Curse of the Goober," are also available to either give you a scoring advantage or to slow down your opponents.

In Solo Mode, you complete a series of progressively difficult challenges that focus on scoring the most points in different scenarios. Bronze, Silver, and Gold medals are awarded for high scores. For every 5 gold medals achieved, the player will also unlock a fancy new Orb to use in Solo or Multiplayer mode.

The Multiplayer Mode allows 2 Orbz players to compete against each other over a local Bluetooth network. Select a course to play, number of rounds in the match, and a time limit.</Description>
		<UserRating>3.25 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Easy</Difficulty>
		<Length>12 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Extreme AI, Inc.</Developer>
		<Genre>Action &gt; General</Genre>
		<Release name="Orbz" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Extreme AI, Inc.</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode> </ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>07/15/04</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Paintball" URL="/zod/953385-paintball">
		<Description>A new, original and very addictive puzzle game! All you have to do is make sets of 3 or more balls of the same color next to a pipe opening! Every color can make sets except black. You'll see the next color, click on the ball which you wish to paint and off you go. Keep an eye on your paint meter though-if you run out of paint, you lose.</Description>
		<UserRating>3.83 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Just Right</Difficulty>
		<Length>2.3 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Crazysoft</Developer>
		<Genre>Puzzle &gt; General</Genre>
		<Release name="Paintball" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Crazysoft</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode> </ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>2004</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Pocket Mini Golf" URL="/zod/953413-pocket-mini-golf">
		<Description>Pocket Mini Golf features 3 courses of increasing difficulty, with 18 holes per course. It has 4 different players to choose from and 3 different game types. Play standard golf rules or against the clock, the choice is yours!</Description>
		<UserRating>4.50 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Easy</Difficulty>
		<Length>10.4 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Mobile Wizardry</Developer>
		<Genre>Sports &gt; Individual &gt; Golf &gt; Arcade</Genre>
		<Release name="Pocket Mini Golf" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Momentum Games</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode> </ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>2003</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Pocket Mini Golf eXtra" URL="/zod/953507-pocket-mini-golf-extra">
		<Description>Pocket Mini Golf eXtra is a Sports game, developed by Mobile Wizardry and published by Momentum Games,  which was released in 2004.</Description>
		<UserRating>4.67 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Easy</Difficulty>
		<Length>9.3 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Mobile Wizardry</Developer>
		<Genre>Sports &gt; Individual &gt; Golf &gt; Sim</Genre>
		<Release name="Pocket Mini Golf eXtra" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Momentum Games</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode> </ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>Q4 2004</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="RifleSLUGS-W: Wild Web Wars" URL="/zod/953414-rifleslugs-w-wild-web-wars">
		<Description>Using a wide range of weapons, the armies engage in fierce battle, attempting to annihilate each other. Command your army of slugs in battle against the computer or another player. Choose from 8 different maps and tons of weapons. You can play with another player via Bluetooth. You can also find a partner for your game by logging in to a special web server via Internet connection.</Description>
		<UserRating>3.88 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Just Right</Difficulty>
		<Length>7.3 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Paragon Software</Developer>
		<Genre>Strategy &gt; General</Genre>
		<Release name="RifleSLUGS-W: Wild Web Wars" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Paragon Software</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode> </ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>2004</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Spy Hunter" URL="/zod/920243-spy-hunter">
		<Description>Get behind the wheel of the G-6155 Interceptor for high-speed, mission-based racing in exotic locales.

While operating your SpyHunter Interceptor, you are relentlessly pursued by hordes of air, ground and water enemies as you battle to accomplish your missions and save the world from the mind of a madman.

A remake of the arcade classic, SpyHunter boasts ultra-realistic 3D graphics, real-world locales and the only vehicle capable of morphing into a boat, jet ski or motorcycle.

Explosive weaponry and impressive defensive mechanisms combine with intense speed and strategy to distinguish SpyHunter from routine combat racers and traditional action racing games.</Description>
		<UserRating>2.83 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Just Right</Difficulty>
		<Length>8 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Fathammer</Developer>
		<Franchise>Spy Hunter</Franchise>
		<Genre>Racing &gt; Arcade &gt; Automobile</Genre>
		<Release name="Spy Hunter" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Midway</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode> </ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>2004</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Street Hoops" URL="/zod/920952-street-hoops">
		<Description>Street Hoops is a Sports game, published by Tapwave,  which was released in 2004.</Description>
		<UserRating>2.90 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Just Right</Difficulty>
		<Length>8 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Tapwave</Developer>
		<Genre>Sports &gt; Team &gt; Basketball &gt; Arcade</Genre>
		<Release name="Street Hoops" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Tapwave</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode> </ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>2004</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="TIGER TEAM: Apache vs. Hind" URL="/zod/953508-tiger-team-apache-vs-hind">
		<Description>TIGER TEAM: Apache vs. Hind is a Simulation game, developed by Pazzazz Games and published by OutLook Entertainment,  which was released in 2004.</Description>
		<UserRating>3.83 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Tough</Difficulty>
		<Length>8 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Pazzazz Games</Developer>
		<Genre>Simulation &gt; Flight &gt; Combat</Genre>
		<Release name="TIGER TEAM: Apache vs. Hind" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>OutLook Entertainment</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode> </ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>Q4 2004</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 4" URL="/zod/920946-tony-hawks-pro-skater-4">
		<Description>Take on the role of legendary skateboarder Tony Hawk and 13 other athletes as they skate through enormous free roaming levels, choose from 190 progressively harder goals and build your character's skills to perform 14 of the greatest skateboarding stunts of all time. The game's enhanced career mode allows players to earn respect and the chance to take on all new pro goals by conquering a skater-specific Pro Challenge based on each skater's personal history.</Description>
		<UserRating>3.75 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Easy</Difficulty>
		<Length>8 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Semi Logic Entertainments, Inc.</Developer>
		<Franchise>Tony Hawk Skateboarding</Franchise>
		<Genre>Sports &gt; Individual &gt; Skate / Skateboard</Genre>
		<Release name="Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 4" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Tapwave</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode> </ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>2004</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Warfare Incorporated" URL="/zod/922042-warfare-incorporated">
		<Description>Warfare Incorporated is set in a future ruled by super corporations engaged in no-holds-barred competition for the resources of the galaxy. The action centers around the newly discovered planet Icarus with its astounding mineral wealth and mysterious alien relics. Players take the role of a junior executive at the underdog ACME Exploration Corporation, discoverer of Icarus, and work their way up the corporate ladder by demonstrating their strategic and tactical skills in a campaign of increasingly challenging missions. Early missions concentrate on resource gathering and combat with ACME's chief rival OMNI Industries and as the game develops other factions and the power of the alien technologies come into play.</Description>
		<UserRating>4.33 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Tough</Difficulty>
		<Length>10.7 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Spiffcode</Developer>
		<Genre>Strategy &gt; Real-Time &gt; General</Genre>
		<Release name="Warfare Incorporated" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Handmark</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode> </ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>10/31/03</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Xploids" URL="/zod/953515-xploids">
		<Description>Xploids is an Action game, developed and published by Little Giant Games,  which was released in 2004.</Description>
		<UserRating>4.63 / 5</UserRating>
		<Difficulty>Tough</Difficulty>
		<Length>9.3 hours</Length>
		<Developer>Little Giant Games</Developer>
		<Genre>Action &gt; Shooter &gt; Third-Person &gt; Arcade</Genre>
		<Release name="Xploids" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Little Giant Games</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode>Online</ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>Q4 2004</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Zodiac" URL="/zod/925733-zodiac">
		<Description>Zodiac is a Hardware game, developed and published by Tapwave,  which was released in 2003.</Description>
		<UserRating>5.00 / 5</UserRating>
		<AKA>Zodiac Hardware (US)</AKA>
		<Developer>Tapwave</Developer>
		<Genre>Hardware &gt; Console</Genre>
		<Release name="Zodiac Hardware" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Tapwave</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode> </ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>2003</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
	<software scraper="GameFAQS" system="Zodiac" name="Zodiac Hardware" URL="/zod/925733-zodiac">
		<Description>Zodiac is a Hardware game, developed and published by Tapwave,  which was released in 2003.</Description>
		<UserRating>5.00 / 5</UserRating>
		<Developer>Tapwave</Developer>
		<Genre>Hardware &gt; Console</Genre>
		<Release name="Zodiac Hardware" region="US">
			<ReleasePublisher>Tapwave</ReleasePublisher>
			<ReleaseProductID> </ReleaseProductID>
			<ReleaseBarCode> </ReleaseBarCode>
			<ReleaseDate>2003</ReleaseDate>
		</Release>
	</software>
</softwarelist>
